[
  {
    "id": "100",
    "qPrompt": "Randomly Determined",
    "options": ["polyvalent", "anomolous", "deterministic", "stochastic"],
    "hint": "Having a random probability distribution or pattern that may be analyzed statistically but may not be predicted precisely.",
    "answer": "stochastic"
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "qPrompt": "A number used to tell how measurements for a group are spread out from the average (mean), or expected value",
    "options": ["Mean", "variance", "skewness", "standard deviation"],
    "hint": "When this is low, it means that most numbers are close to the average.",
    "answer": "standard deviation"
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "qPrompt": "Prompt3",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡­", "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¾", "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡ª", "ğŸ‡°ğŸ‡µ"],
    "hint": "It contains red.",
    "answer": "ğŸ‡°ğŸ‡µ"
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "qPrompt": "Prompt4",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡­", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡¿", "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡°", "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¬"],
    "hint": "It contains green.",
    "answer": "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡¿"
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "qPrompt": "Prompt5",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡©", "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡³", "ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡«", "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡·"],
    "hint": "It contains white.",
    "answer": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡·"
  },
  {
    "id": "105",
    "qPrompt": "Prompt6",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡´", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡¹", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡¬"],
    "hint": "It contains red.",
    "answer": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¦"
  },
  {
    "id": "106",
    "qPrompt": "Prompt7",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¿", "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡¿", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡´", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡°"],
    "hint": "It contains stripes.",
    "answer": "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¿"
  },
  {
    "id": "107",
    "qPrompt": "Prompt8",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡·", "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡±", "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡­"],
    "hint": "It contains red.",
    "answer": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡­"
  },
  {
    "id": "108",
    "qPrompt": "Prompt9",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡ª", "ğŸ‡»ğŸ‡¨", "ğŸ´ó §ó ¢ó ³ó £ó ´ó ¿"],
    "hint": "It contains green.",
    "answer": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡ª"
  },
  {
    "id": "109",
    "qPrompt": "Prompt10",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡¼", "ğŸ‡«ğŸ‡´", "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡ª"],
    "hint": "It contains blue.",
    "answer": "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦"
  }
]
